回到Rato所说，frame布局、linear布局、relative布局，
Going back to what Rato said, frame layout, linear layout, and relative layout
这三种布局将会是你在构建UI时最常遇见的。
are three of the most common layouts you will use in building out your UI.
这些都是来自view group类，是用来监管子视图的。
These all descend from the view group class, designed to contain and
每一种布局都有各自的优势，
give order to child views. They each have their strengths and
你应该尝试去使用它们，并为你的程序找到最优布局。
you should always try to use this simplest layout that will get the job done.
Frame Layout非常适合简单的布局，当你只有一个子视图时，
Frame Layout is great for simple layouts when you only have one child to view,
例如一个内容区域只有列表视图的情况。
like a list view that fills the entire content area. Linear layout is
Linear Layout能够完美处理视图内容的水平或者垂直堆叠，一个接着一个的堆叠，
perfect for stacking the views vertically or horizontally, one after another,
它也是能够打破比例来显示的唯一的方法。
it is also the only way to break up the display proportionately. Relative layout
Relative Layout相较于别的布局来说更为强大，当然也更为复杂。
is powerful but a bit more complicated compared to the others. Throw a bunch of
抛开relative layout里的一堆视图，你可以对每一个视图对应的父类进行配置，
views inside a relative layout, and then you can configure each views
也可以是relative布局，同级视图，这将给你很多种选择的机会。
position relative to parent, the relative layout, or to sibling views, tons of
当我们构建更复杂的屏幕时，我们会更加详细的讨论布局。
possibilities. We'll explore these layouts in greater detail when we build more
现在让我们回到预期表。
complex screens. For now, let's get back to building our forecast list.